Taimoor Tariq

Full-Stack Developer

Profile

Full-Stack Developer. Currently enrolled at Carleton University, I have been creating applications since high school. Having created a wide variety of programs and am capable of implementing my ideas into practical programs. With my experience working on a large number of team projects, I've developed great teamwork and leadership skills that would be very valuable for me when settling into new work environments.

Employment History

Tim Hortons

Ottawa, ON | Aug 2021 - Present

Working part-time taking and serving orders both at the store front and drive-thru.

Lead Developer at Ontario Post Secondary Esports

Ottawa, ON | Sep 2020 - Present

Developed an automated system to host and record the tournament games. I currently look after the system and make sure everything goes smoothly or if any additional features are required to be implemented.

IT Manager at Wichita Wolves Esports

Worked from home | Oct 2019 - Oct 2021

Developed a website and a discord bot (web application) for the Wichita Wolves, an Esports Organization based in the city of Wichita, Kansas. I joined the organization in October 2019 and handled all their Technology related matters.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science at Carleton University

Ottawa, ON | Sep 2018 - Present

A-Level at Merryland International School

Abu Dhabi, UAE | Sep 2004 - Jun 2018

Details

- ▼ taimoortarig2000@gmail.com
- +1 (343) 988-6694
- Ottawa, Canada
- Oct 05, 2000
- taimoor.me
- @Taimoor-Tariq
- @_TaimoorTariq
- in in/MuhammadTaimoorTariq

Skills



Dev Skills

🖬 csss

🕸 REACT



6 LUA

■ BOOTSTRAP